[
    {
        "question": "An egg-laying Australian mammal.",
        "choices": [
            "Duck-billed platypus",
            "Bat"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "An African bird which lays the biggest eggs.",
        "choices": [
            "Emu",
            "Ostrich"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The animal having two humps.",
        "choices": [
            "Bactrian camel",
            "Arabian camel"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The creature which is called the great dam-builder and gnaws through trees.",
        "choices": [
            "Beaver",
            "Sloth"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Name of the American vulture.",
        "choices": [
            "Kingfisher",
            "Condor"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The emperor birds found in the Antarctica.",
        "choices": [
            "Wallaroos",
            "Penguins"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "An animal that is a deadly enemy of snakes.",
        "choices": [
            "Frog",
            "Mongoose"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "'Pen' and the 'cob' are the genders of which water bird?",
        "choices": [
            "Swan",
            "Duck"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The animal that survives on bamboo shoots and lives mainly in the mountains of Western China.",
        "choices": [
            "Dingo",
            "Giant Panda"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "An Australian marsupial that carries its baby in its pouch.",
        "choices": [
            "Kangaroo",
            "Kiwi"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 0
    }
]